{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "13, -13", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 169 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 169\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(169) or x \u003d -√(169)\nx \u003d +13 or x \u003d -13", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 169 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "29, -29", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 841 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 841\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(841) or x \u003d -√(841)\nx \u003d +29 or x \u003d -29", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 841 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "13, -13", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 169 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 169\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(169) or x \u003d -√(169)\nx \u003d +13 or x \u003d -13", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 169 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1 + √(2), -1 - √(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n9(x + 1)^2 - 18 \u003d 0\n9(x + 1)^2 \u003d 18\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 1)^2 \u003d 2\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 1 \u003d +√(2) or x + 1 \u003d -√(2)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n9(x + 1)^2 - 18 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "17, -17", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 289 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 289\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(289) or x \u003d -√(289)\nx \u003d +17 or x \u003d -17", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 289 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, -5", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n10(x + 2)^2 - 90 \u003d 0\n10(x + 2)^2 \u003d 90\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 9\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 2 \u003d +√(9) or x + 2 \u003d -√(9)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n10(x + 2)^2 - 90 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "13, -13", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 169 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 169\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(169) or x \u003d -√(169)\nx \u003d +13 or x \u003d -13", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 169 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, -1", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n3(x - 1)^2 - 12 \u003d 0\n3(x - 1)^2 \u003d 12\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 1)^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 1 \u003d + √(4) or x - 1 \u003d - √(4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3(x - 1)^2 - 12 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11, -11", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 121 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 121\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(121) or x \u003d -√(121)\nx \u003d +11 or x \u003d -11", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 121 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, 0", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n3(x - 2)^2 - 12 \u003d 0\n3(x - 2)^2 \u003d 12\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 2)^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 2 \u003d + √(4) or x - 2 \u003d - √(4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3(x - 2)^2 - 12 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3, -9", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n5(x + 6)^2 - 45 \u003d 0\n5(x + 6)^2 \u003d 45\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 6)^2 \u003d 9\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 6 \u003d +√(9) or x + 6 \u003d -√(9)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n5(x + 6)^2 - 45 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "26, -26", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 676 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 676\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(676) or x \u003d -√(676)\nx \u003d +26 or x \u003d -26", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 676 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -2", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 4 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(4) or x \u003d -√(4)\nx \u003d +2 or x \u003d -2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 4 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9 + √(6), -9 - √(6)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n11(x + 9)^2 - 66 \u003d 0\n11(x + 9)^2 \u003d 66\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 9)^2 \u003d 6\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 9 \u003d +√(6) or x + 9 \u003d -√(6)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n11(x + 9)^2 - 66 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6, -6", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 36 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 36\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(36) or x \u003d -√(36)\nx \u003d +6 or x \u003d -6", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 36 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 1 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(1) or x \u003d -√(1)\nx \u003d +1 or x \u003d -1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 1 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7 + √(5), 7 - √(5)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n10(x - 7)^2 - 50 \u003d 0\n10(x - 7)^2 \u003d 50\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 7)^2 \u003d 5\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 7 \u003d + √(5) or x - 7 \u003d - √(5)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n10(x - 7)^2 - 50 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2 + √(3), -2 - √(3)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x + 2)^2 - 21 \u003d 0\n7(x + 2)^2 \u003d 21\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 3\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 2 \u003d +√(3) or x + 2 \u003d -√(3)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x + 2)^2 - 21 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6, 0", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n11(x - 3)^2 - 99 \u003d 0\n11(x - 3)^2 \u003d 99\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 3)^2 \u003d 9\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 3 \u003d + √(9) or x - 3 \u003d - √(9)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n11(x - 3)^2 - 99 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "17, -17", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 289 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 289\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(289) or x \u003d -√(289)\nx \u003d +17 or x \u003d -17", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 289 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7 + √(8), -7 - √(8)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n4(x + 7)^2 - 32 \u003d 0\n4(x + 7)^2 \u003d 32\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 7)^2 \u003d 8\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 7 \u003d +√(8) or x + 7 \u003d -√(8)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n4(x + 7)^2 - 32 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4 + √(7), -4 - √(7)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n11(x + 4)^2 - 77 \u003d 0\n11(x + 4)^2 \u003d 77\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 4)^2 \u003d 7\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 4 \u003d +√(7) or x + 4 \u003d -√(7)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n11(x + 4)^2 - 77 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11, -11", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 121 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 121\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(121) or x \u003d -√(121)\nx \u003d +11 or x \u003d -11", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 121 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0, -6", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n10(x + 3)^2 - 90 \u003d 0\n10(x + 3)^2 \u003d 90\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 9\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 3 \u003d +√(9) or x + 3 \u003d -√(9)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n10(x + 3)^2 - 90 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7, -11", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n2(x + 9)^2 - 8 \u003d 0\n2(x + 9)^2 \u003d 8\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 9)^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 9 \u003d +√(4) or x + 9 \u003d -√(4)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2(x + 9)^2 - 8 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9, -9", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 81 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 81\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(81) or x \u003d -√(81)\nx \u003d +9 or x \u003d -9", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 81 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8, -12", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n2(x + 10)^2 - 8 \u003d 0\n2(x + 10)^2 \u003d 8\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 10)^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 10 \u003d +√(4) or x + 10 \u003d -√(4)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2(x + 10)^2 - 8 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7, 1", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n11(x - 4)^2 - 99 \u003d 0\n11(x - 4)^2 \u003d 99\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 4)^2 \u003d 9\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 4 \u003d + √(9) or x - 4 \u003d - √(9)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n11(x - 4)^2 - 99 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7 + √(5), 7 - √(5)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n10(x - 7)^2 - 50 \u003d 0\n10(x - 7)^2 \u003d 50\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 7)^2 \u003d 5\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 7 \u003d + √(5) or x - 7 \u003d - √(5)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n10(x - 7)^2 - 50 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5, 3", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n5(x - 4)^2 - 5 \u003d 0\n5(x - 4)^2 \u003d 5\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 4)^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 4 \u003d + √(1) or x - 4 \u003d - √(1)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n5(x - 4)^2 - 5 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8 + √(5), 8 - √(5)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x - 8)^2 - 35 \u003d 0\n7(x - 8)^2 \u003d 35\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 8)^2 \u003d 5\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 8 \u003d + √(5) or x - 8 \u003d - √(5)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x - 8)^2 - 35 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6, 2", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n6(x - 4)^2 - 24 \u003d 0\n6(x - 4)^2 \u003d 24\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 4)^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 4 \u003d + √(4) or x - 4 \u003d - √(4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n6(x - 4)^2 - 24 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0, -2", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n5(x + 1)^2 - 5 \u003d 0\n5(x + 1)^2 \u003d 5\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 1)^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 1 \u003d +√(1) or x + 1 \u003d -√(1)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n5(x + 1)^2 - 5 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7 + √(8), 7 - √(8)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n10(x - 7)^2 - 80 \u003d 0\n10(x - 7)^2 \u003d 80\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 7)^2 \u003d 8\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 7 \u003d + √(8) or x - 7 \u003d - √(8)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n10(x - 7)^2 - 80 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6 + √(7), -6 - √(7)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n6(x + 6)^2 - 42 \u003d 0\n6(x + 6)^2 \u003d 42\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 6)^2 \u003d 7\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 6 \u003d +√(7) or x + 6 \u003d -√(7)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n6(x + 6)^2 - 42 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "17, -17", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 289 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 289\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(289) or x \u003d -√(289)\nx \u003d +17 or x \u003d -17", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 289 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5 + √(5), -5 - √(5)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x + 5)^2 - 35 \u003d 0\n7(x + 5)^2 \u003d 35\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 5)^2 \u003d 5\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 5 \u003d +√(5) or x + 5 \u003d -√(5)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x + 5)^2 - 35 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7 + √(6), 7 - √(6)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n8(x - 7)^2 - 48 \u003d 0\n8(x - 7)^2 \u003d 48\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 7)^2 \u003d 6\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 7 \u003d + √(6) or x - 7 \u003d - √(6)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n8(x - 7)^2 - 48 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4 + √(2), 4 - √(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n5(x - 4)^2 - 10 \u003d 0\n5(x - 4)^2 \u003d 10\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 4)^2 \u003d 2\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 4 \u003d + √(2) or x - 4 \u003d - √(2)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n5(x - 4)^2 - 10 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10 + √(7), 10 - √(7)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n11(x - 10)^2 - 77 \u003d 0\n11(x - 10)^2 \u003d 77\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 10)^2 \u003d 7\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 10 \u003d + √(7) or x - 10 \u003d - √(7)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n11(x - 10)^2 - 77 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "20, -20", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 400\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(400) or x \u003d -√(400)\nx \u003d +20 or x \u003d -20", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -2", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 4 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(4) or x \u003d -√(4)\nx \u003d +2 or x \u003d -2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 4 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10, -10", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 100 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 100\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(100) or x \u003d -√(100)\nx \u003d +10 or x \u003d -10", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 100 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5 + √(2), 5 - √(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n2(x - 5)^2 - 4 \u003d 0\n2(x - 5)^2 \u003d 4\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 5)^2 \u003d 2\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 5 \u003d + √(2) or x - 5 \u003d - √(2)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2(x - 5)^2 - 4 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1, -1", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 1 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(1) or x \u003d -√(1)\nx \u003d +1 or x \u003d -1", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 1 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10 + √(6), 10 - √(6)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n11(x - 10)^2 - 66 \u003d 0\n11(x - 10)^2 \u003d 66\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 10)^2 \u003d 6\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 10 \u003d + √(6) or x - 10 \u003d - √(6)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n11(x - 10)^2 - 66 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4 + √(3), 4 - √(3)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n4(x - 4)^2 - 12 \u003d 0\n4(x - 4)^2 \u003d 12\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 4)^2 \u003d 3\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 4 \u003d + √(3) or x - 4 \u003d - √(3)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n4(x - 4)^2 - 12 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7, -7", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 49 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 49\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(49) or x \u003d -√(49)\nx \u003d +7 or x \u003d -7", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 49 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6 + √(6), 6 - √(6)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n2(x - 6)^2 - 12 \u003d 0\n2(x - 6)^2 \u003d 12\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 6)^2 \u003d 6\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 6 \u003d + √(6) or x - 6 \u003d - √(6)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n2(x - 6)^2 - 12 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2 + √(10), -2 - √(10)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n9(x + 2)^2 - 90 \u003d 0\n9(x + 2)^2 \u003d 90\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 10\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 2 \u003d +√(10) or x + 2 \u003d -√(10)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n9(x + 2)^2 - 90 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, -3", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 9 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 9\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(9) or x \u003d -√(9)\nx \u003d +3 or x \u003d -3", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 9 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5, -5", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 25 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 25\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(25) or x \u003d -√(25)\nx \u003d +5 or x \u003d -5", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 25 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, -4", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 16 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 16\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(16) or x \u003d -√(16)\nx \u003d +4 or x \u003d -4", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 16 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11, -11", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 121 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 121\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(121) or x \u003d -√(121)\nx \u003d +11 or x \u003d -11", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 121 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9, -9", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 81 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 81\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(81) or x \u003d -√(81)\nx \u003d +9 or x \u003d -9", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 81 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4 + √(7), -4 - √(7)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n8(x + 4)^2 - 56 \u003d 0\n8(x + 4)^2 \u003d 56\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 4)^2 \u003d 7\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 4 \u003d +√(7) or x + 4 \u003d -√(7)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n8(x + 4)^2 - 56 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5, -11", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n11(x + 8)^2 - 99 \u003d 0\n11(x + 8)^2 \u003d 99\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 8)^2 \u003d 9\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 8 \u003d +√(9) or x + 8 \u003d -√(9)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n11(x + 8)^2 - 99 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "21, -21", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 441 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 441\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(441) or x \u003d -√(441)\nx \u003d +21 or x \u003d -21", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 441 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-10 + √(2), -10 - √(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n5(x + 10)^2 - 10 \u003d 0\n5(x + 10)^2 \u003d 10\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 10)^2 \u003d 2\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 10 \u003d +√(2) or x + 10 \u003d -√(2)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n5(x + 10)^2 - 10 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4 + √(3), 4 - √(3)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x - 4)^2 - 21 \u003d 0\n7(x - 4)^2 \u003d 21\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 4)^2 \u003d 3\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 4 \u003d + √(3) or x - 4 \u003d - √(3)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x - 4)^2 - 21 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11, 7", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n4(x - 9)^2 - 16 \u003d 0\n4(x - 9)^2 \u003d 16\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 9)^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 9 \u003d + √(4) or x - 9 \u003d - √(4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n4(x - 9)^2 - 16 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2 + √(10), -2 - √(10)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n10(x + 2)^2 - 100 \u003d 0\n10(x + 2)^2 \u003d 100\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 10\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 2 \u003d +√(10) or x + 2 \u003d -√(10)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n10(x + 2)^2 - 100 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8 + √(7), -8 - √(7)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n4(x + 8)^2 - 28 \u003d 0\n4(x + 8)^2 \u003d 28\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 8)^2 \u003d 7\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 8 \u003d +√(7) or x + 8 \u003d -√(7)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n4(x + 8)^2 - 28 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -2", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 4 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(4) or x \u003d -√(4)\nx \u003d +2 or x \u003d -2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 4 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8 + √(5), 8 - √(5)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n11(x - 8)^2 - 55 \u003d 0\n11(x - 8)^2 \u003d 55\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 8)^2 \u003d 5\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 8 \u003d + √(5) or x - 8 \u003d - √(5)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n11(x - 8)^2 - 55 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6 + √(5), -6 - √(5)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n11(x + 6)^2 - 55 \u003d 0\n11(x + 6)^2 \u003d 55\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 6)^2 \u003d 5\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 6 \u003d +√(5) or x + 6 \u003d -√(5)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n11(x + 6)^2 - 55 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3 + √(7), 3 - √(7)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n10(x - 3)^2 - 70 \u003d 0\n10(x - 3)^2 \u003d 70\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 3)^2 \u003d 7\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 3 \u003d + √(7) or x - 3 \u003d - √(7)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n10(x - 3)^2 - 70 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3 + √(7), 3 - √(7)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n8(x - 3)^2 - 56 \u003d 0\n8(x - 3)^2 \u003d 56\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 3)^2 \u003d 7\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 3 \u003d + √(7) or x - 3 \u003d - √(7)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n8(x - 3)^2 - 56 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2, -4", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n10(x + 3)^2 - 10 \u003d 0\n10(x + 3)^2 \u003d 10\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 3)^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 3 \u003d +√(1) or x + 3 \u003d -√(1)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n10(x + 3)^2 - 10 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4 + √(8), 4 - √(8)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n9(x - 4)^2 - 72 \u003d 0\n9(x - 4)^2 \u003d 72\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 4)^2 \u003d 8\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 4 \u003d + √(8) or x - 4 \u003d - √(8)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n9(x - 4)^2 - 72 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14, -14", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 196 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 196\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(196) or x \u003d -√(196)\nx \u003d +14 or x \u003d -14", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 196 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, -3", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 9 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 9\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(9) or x \u003d -√(9)\nx \u003d +3 or x \u003d -3", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 9 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "27, -27", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 729 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 729\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(729) or x \u003d -√(729)\nx \u003d +27 or x \u003d -27", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 729 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1 + √(3), 1 - √(3)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n11(x - 1)^2 - 33 \u003d 0\n11(x - 1)^2 \u003d 33\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 1)^2 \u003d 3\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 1 \u003d + √(3) or x - 1 \u003d - √(3)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n11(x - 1)^2 - 33 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14, -14", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 196 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 196\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(196) or x \u003d -√(196)\nx \u003d +14 or x \u003d -14", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 196 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "20, -20", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 400\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(400) or x \u003d -√(400)\nx \u003d +20 or x \u003d -20", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 400 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9 + √(8), -9 - √(8)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n8(x + 9)^2 - 64 \u003d 0\n8(x + 9)^2 \u003d 64\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 9)^2 \u003d 8\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 9 \u003d +√(8) or x + 9 \u003d -√(8)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n8(x + 9)^2 - 64 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "25, -25", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 625 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 625\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(625) or x \u003d -√(625)\nx \u003d +25 or x \u003d -25", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 625 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0, -4", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n11(x + 2)^2 - 44 \u003d 0\n11(x + 2)^2 \u003d 44\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 2 \u003d +√(4) or x + 2 \u003d -√(4)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n11(x + 2)^2 - 44 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "25, -25", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 625 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 625\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(625) or x \u003d -√(625)\nx \u003d +25 or x \u003d -25", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 625 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5 + √(6), -5 - √(6)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n11(x + 5)^2 - 66 \u003d 0\n11(x + 5)^2 \u003d 66\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 5)^2 \u003d 6\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 5 \u003d +√(6) or x + 5 \u003d -√(6)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n11(x + 5)^2 - 66 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "27, -27", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 729 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 729\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(729) or x \u003d -√(729)\nx \u003d +27 or x \u003d -27", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 729 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, 0", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n3(x - 1)^2 - 3 \u003d 0\n3(x - 1)^2 \u003d 3\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 1)^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 1 \u003d + √(1) or x - 1 \u003d - √(1)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3(x - 1)^2 - 3 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7, 3", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n11(x - 5)^2 - 44 \u003d 0\n11(x - 5)^2 \u003d 44\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 5)^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 5 \u003d + √(4) or x - 5 \u003d - √(4)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n11(x - 5)^2 - 44 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4 + √(8), 4 - √(8)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n4(x - 4)^2 - 32 \u003d 0\n4(x - 4)^2 \u003d 32\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 4)^2 \u003d 8\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 4 \u003d + √(8) or x - 4 \u003d - √(8)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n4(x - 4)^2 - 32 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1 + √(7), 1 - √(7)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n11(x - 1)^2 - 77 \u003d 0\n11(x - 1)^2 \u003d 77\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 1)^2 \u003d 7\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 1 \u003d + √(7) or x - 1 \u003d - √(7)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n11(x - 1)^2 - 77 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4 + √(2), -4 - √(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n4(x + 4)^2 - 8 \u003d 0\n4(x + 4)^2 \u003d 8\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 4)^2 \u003d 2\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 4 \u003d +√(2) or x + 4 \u003d -√(2)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n4(x + 4)^2 - 8 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7, -9", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n8(x + 8)^2 - 8 \u003d 0\n8(x + 8)^2 \u003d 8\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 8)^2 \u003d 1\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 8 \u003d +√(1) or x + 8 \u003d -√(1)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n8(x + 8)^2 - 8 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12, 6", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n5(x - 9)^2 - 45 \u003d 0\n5(x - 9)^2 \u003d 45\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 9)^2 \u003d 9\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 9 \u003d + √(9) or x - 9 \u003d - √(9)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n5(x - 9)^2 - 45 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8 + √(2), -8 - √(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x + 8)^2 - 14 \u003d 0\n7(x + 8)^2 \u003d 14\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 8)^2 \u003d 2\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 8 \u003d +√(2) or x + 8 \u003d -√(2)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x + 8)^2 - 14 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "13, -13", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 169 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 169\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(169) or x \u003d -√(169)\nx \u003d +13 or x \u003d -13", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 169 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -2", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 4 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 4\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(4) or x \u003d -√(4)\nx \u003d +2 or x \u003d -2", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 4 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2 + √(8), -2 - √(8)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n5(x + 2)^2 - 40 \u003d 0\n5(x + 2)^2 \u003d 40\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 2)^2 \u003d 8\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 2 \u003d +√(8) or x + 2 \u003d -√(8)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n5(x + 2)^2 - 40 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8 + √(2), -8 - √(2)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n9(x + 8)^2 - 18 \u003d 0\n9(x + 8)^2 \u003d 18\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 8)^2 \u003d 2\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 8 \u003d +√(2) or x + 8 \u003d -√(2)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n9(x + 8)^2 - 18 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6 + √(8), 6 - √(8)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x - 6)^2 - 56 \u003d 0\n7(x - 6)^2 \u003d 56\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 6)^2 \u003d 8\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 6 \u003d + √(8) or x - 6 \u003d - √(8)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x - 6)^2 - 56 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4 + √(10), 4 - √(10)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n3(x - 4)^2 - 30 \u003d 0\n3(x - 4)^2 \u003d 30\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 4)^2 \u003d 10\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 4 \u003d + √(10) or x - 4 \u003d - √(10)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n3(x - 4)^2 - 30 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9 + √(10), -9 - √(10)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n8(x + 9)^2 - 80 \u003d 0\n8(x + 9)^2 \u003d 80\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 9)^2 \u003d 10\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 9 \u003d +√(10) or x + 9 \u003d -√(10)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n8(x + 9)^2 - 80 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10 + √(5), 10 - √(5)", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n7(x - 10)^2 - 35 \u003d 0\n7(x - 10)^2 \u003d 35\nDivide both sides by the coefficient\n(x - 10)^2 \u003d 5\nNext, apply the square root property\nx - 10 \u003d + √(5) or x - 10 \u003d - √(5)\nSimplify and Solve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n7(x - 10)^2 - 35 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, -4", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\n9(x + 1)^2 - 81 \u003d 0\n9(x + 1)^2 \u003d 81\nDivide both sides by the the coefficient\n(x + 1)^2 \u003d 9\nNext, apply the square root property\nx + 1 \u003d +√(9) or x + 1 \u003d -√(9)\nSolve for x", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Solve for x:\n9(x + 1)^2 - 81 \u003d 0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "28, -28", "explanation": "Begin by isolating the square\nx^2 - 784 \u003d 0\nx^2 \u003d 784\nNext, apply the square root property\nx \u003d +√(784) or x \u003d -√(784)\nx \u003d +28 or x \u003d -28", "prompt": "x \u003d", "question": "Extract the roots of:\nx^2 - 784 \u003d 0", "type": "text"}
]}